A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York Board of Rabbis - New York City, May 5, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1505)
  Dedication of the Training and Inter-faith Human Relations Center.
- Seraphic Secretaries of America - 26th Anniversary Bosses' Dinner - New York City, May 5, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1506)
- Westchester County Women's Republican Club - Eastchester, New York, May 5, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1507)
- Delaware River Basin Commission - Annual Dinner - Trenton, New Jersey, May 6, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1508)
- Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 6, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1509)
- St. Agnes Hospital - White Plains, New York, May 7, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1510)
  Dedication of new wing.
- New York State Council of Chemical Industry - Steering Committee Dinner - Albany, New York, May 9, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1511)
- International Conference on Condensation Nuclei - State University at Albany - Albany, New York, May 9, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1512)
- Pulitzer Prizes - 50th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, May 10, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1513)
- Mayor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - 11th Annual Dinner - New York City, May 10, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1514)
- State University at New Paltz - Ulster County, New York, May 11, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1515)
- Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, Inc. - New Paltz, New York, May 11, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1516)
- Jewish Theological Seminary Lunch - New York City - Cancelled, May 12, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1517)
- Pre-White House Conference - New York City, May 12, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1518)
- Nassau County Republican Committee - Great Neck, New York, May 12, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1519)
- Co-Op City - Ground-breaking Ceremony - Bronx, New York, May 14, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1520)
- Putnam County Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - Peekskill, New York, May 14, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1521)
- Beth Israel Medical Center - New York City, May 15, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1522)
  Dedication of Linsky Pavilion.
- Greek Independence Day Parade - New York City, May 15, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1523)
- Norwegian-American 17th of May Committee - Brooklyn, New York, May 15, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1524)
- Brotherhood-In-Action - Dedication Dinner - New York City, May 16, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1525)
- Water Treatment Plant - Troy, New York, May 16, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1526)
  Dedication ceremony.
- Governor's Awards - Schenectady, New York, May 17, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1527)
  "For a More Beautiful New York" presentation ceremony.
- Route 17 Association - Luncheon - Elmira, New York, May 17, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1528)
  NAR did not attend.
- Arts Council of America - New York City, May 19, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1529)
- Cayuga County Republican Committee, May 19, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1530)
- Lyndhurst - Dedication - Tarrytown, New York, May 20, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1531)
- Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs - Livingston Manor, New York, May 20, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1532)
- New York City Central Labor Council - Educational Conference - New York City, May 21, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1533)
- Orvil E. Dryfoos Conference on Public Affairs - Hanover, New Hampshire - Cancelled, May 21, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1534)
- Veteran's Association, 369th Division - Parade - New York City, May 22, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1535)
- Nassau County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Dinner - Garden City, New York, May 23, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1536)
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, May 24, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1537)
- New York State Health Department - Annual Conference, May 24, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1538)
  William J. Ronan in behalf of NAR.
- Chamber of Commerce - New York City, May 25, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1539)
- National Council of Negro Women - Premiere Life Membership Dinner - New York City - Cancelled, May 25, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1540)
- American Federation of Art Galleries, May 26, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1541)
  Reception, Carborundum Co.
- Cerebral Palsy Association - Queens Village, May 26, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1542)
  Testimonial - Nat H. Hentel.
- Conference on Women - New York City, May 26-27, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1543)
- Cornerstone Baptist Church - Dedication - Brooklyn, New York, May 29, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1544)
- New York State Association of the Improved Benevolent Protective Order of Elks - Convention - New York City, May 29, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1545)
- New York Medical College - New York City, June 1, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1546)
  Commencement, honorary degree, Hunter College.
- Yates County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Dinner - Penn Yan, New York, June 2, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1547)
- Governor's Conference on Manpower Training - Buffalo, New York, June 2, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1548)
- Federation of American-Hellenic Societies of Greater New York - Educational Progressive Dinner - New York City, June 4, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1549)
- Union College - Commencement - Schenectady, New York, June 5, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1550)
- Syracuse University - Syracuse, New York, June 5, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1551)
  Commencement, honorary degree.
- Twenty/Thirty Year Club - Rockefeller Center - New York City - Cancelled, June 6, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1552)
  15th anniversary, founding, w/Happy.
- Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry and Long Island Federation of Labor (AFL-CIO) - Garden City, Long Island, New York, June 7, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1553)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Water Pollution Control Conference - New York City, June 8, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1554)
- New York Republican State Committee - Annual Dinner - New York City, June 9, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1555)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Breakfast - New York City, June 9, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1556)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - New York City, June 9, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1557)
  Local #3 reception, meeting.
- Symposium on "Fresh Water of New York State" - Buffalo, New York, June 13, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1558)
- Rockland County Republican Committee - Dinner, June 14, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1559)
- Brookhaven Laboratory - Upton, Long Island, New York, June 15, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1560)
  Luncheon, accelerator site.
- New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officials - Grossinger, New York, June 15, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1560A)
- Saratoga Springs State Park - Saratoga Springs, New York, June 16, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1561)
  Dedication of the Saratoga Performing Arts Center.
- National Association for Retarded Children, Nassau County Chapter - Annual Fund Raiser - New York City, June 18, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1562)
- Bronx County Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - Bronx, New York, June 18, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1563)
- State University of New York, Albany - Commencement - Albany, New York, June 19, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1564)
- Rensselaer County Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - Averill Park, New York, June 20, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1565)
- Governor's Reception for Japanese Ambassador - New York City, June 22, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1566)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - 47th Annual State Convention - Dinner - Rochester, New York, June 23, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1567)
- Announcement re: New York State Commerce Department Office in Tokyo, Japan, June 24, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1568)
- Dinner Honoring Mayors and Legislators of Puerto Rico - New York City, June 25, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1569)
- New York State Association of Broadcasters - Cooperstown, New York, June 28, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1570)
  Executive and 5th annual conference.
- Supervisors Association of the State of New York - Saratoga, New York, June 28, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1571)
- Empire Girls State - 25th Annual Session - Albany, New York, June 28, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1572)
- Brookwood Nuclear Power Plant - Brookwood, New York, June 29, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1573)
  Official opening of the Science Information Center.
- Medical Facilities Development Program, June 29, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1574)
- NAR Remarks re: Medicare - Mt. Sinai Hospital, New York City, July 1, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1575)
- NAR Remarks re: Medicare - Mt. Sinai Hospital, New York City, July 29, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1576)
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, August 1, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1577)
  Dinner for President Shazar of Israel.
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Housewives for Rockefeller Team Committee - New York City, August 4, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1578)
- Niagara Frontier Port Authority Bill Signing Ceremony - Buffalo, New York, August 4, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1579)
- Saratoga Springs State Park - Saratoga Springs, New York, August 4, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1580)
  Opening concert, Philadelphia Orchestra.
- 189th Anniversary of the Battle of Oriskany, August 6, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1581)
  Ceremony, parade.
- 78th Annual Boonville Fair - Boonville, New York, August 6, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1582)
- Jefferson County Fair - Watertown, New York, August 6, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1583)
- Jefferson County - Rural Citizens for Rockefeller Dinner - Watertown, New York, August 6, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1584)
- German Day - West Seneca, New York, August 7, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1585)
  Parade, ceremony, St. John's Orphanage.
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - Disabled American Veterans 45th National Convention - New York City, August 9, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1586)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - New York City, August 9, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1587)
  Opening of store fronts in New York City, Brooklyn, Queens, Bronx.
- Wayne County Republican Committee, August 10, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1588)
- Ontario County Republican Committee - Canandaigua, New York, August 10, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1589)
- A.M.A. Institute - Hamilton, New York - Cancelled, August 10, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1590)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Empire State Potato Field Day and Farm Materials Exhibition - Honeoye Falls, New York, August 10, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1591)
  33rd annual exhibition; no speech.
- Rotary Club Luncheon - Glens Falls, New York, August 11, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1592)
- Speculator, New York, August 11, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1593)
- Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs - Saratoga, New York, August 11, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1594)
  TARS of Politics banquet.
- Saratoga County Republican Committee - Saratoga Springs, New York, August 11, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1595)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Brooklyn, New York, August 13, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1596)
  Tour Brooklyn beaches; rally.
- Orange County Republican Committee - Middletown, New York, August 14, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1597)
  Festival and Reception.
- Chemung County Fair - Horseheads, New York, August 16, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1598)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Buffalo, New York, August 16, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1599)
  Opening of Western New York campaign headquarters; reception.
- Amherst Republican Committee - Williamsville, New York, August 16, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1600)
- New York State Odd Fellows - 130th Annual Convention - Buffalo, New York, August 17, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1601)
- Polish Union of America - National Convention - Niagara Falls, New York, August 17, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1602)
- Monroe County Fair - Henrietta, New York, August 17, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1603)
- Camp Smith - Peekskill, New York, August 19, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1604)
  Rededication, review, graduation.
- Herkimer County Fair - Frankfort, New York, August 19, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1605)
- Altamont Fair, August 19, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1606)
  Dinner, fair and exhibits.
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - National Convention - New York City, August 22, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1607)
- Nassau County Republican Committee - Garden City, New York, August 22, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1608)
- Kiwanis - Malone, New York, August 23, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1609)
- Cornell University - Lake Placid, New York, August 23, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1610)
  Visits Cornell-Uihlein Foundation Potato Seed Farm.
- Essex County Republican Committee - Lake Placid, New York, August 23, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1611)
- Wyoming County Fair - Pike, New York, August 24, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1612)
- Erie County Fair - Hamburg, New York, August 24, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1613)
  Polish Millennium Day luncheon.
- Genesee County Republican Committee - Young Republicans Buffet - Alexander, New York, August 24, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1614)
- Livingston County Republican Committee - Breakfast - Dansville, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1615)
- Yates County Republican Committee - Penn Yan, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1616)
  Reception and rally.
- Schuyler County Republican Committee - Watkins Glen, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1617)
- Visit to Union Park - Hornell, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1618)
- Hornell Board of Education - Luncheon - Hornell, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1619)
- Steuben County Fair - Bath, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1620)
- Town Highway Superintendents and Town Officers - Bath, New York, August 25, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1621)
- Washington County Fair - Greenwich, New York, August 26, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1622)
- Dutchess County Fair - Rhinebeck, New York, August 26, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1623)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - New York City, August 29, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1624)
  Storefront openings.
- Suffolk County Republican Convention Club - New York City, August 30, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1625)
- Statement at Meeting of Steering Committee of New York State Congressional Delegation with U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, August 30, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1626)
  Presented by Oliver Townsend.
- Visit to Moffitt Beach - Speculator, New York, August 31, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1627)
- Northway - Opening of Warrensburg Section, August 31, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1628)
- Syracuse Chamber of Commerce - Syracuse, New York, August 31, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1629)
  Annual State Farm dinner.
- State Fair - Governor's Day - Syracuse, New York, September 1, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1630)
  General Greeting.
- State Fair - Syracuse, New York, September 1, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1631)
  Governor's Day luncheon, speak, R.
- Rensselaer County Fair - Schaghticoke, New York, September 2, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1632)
- Columbia County Fair - Chatham, New York, September 2, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1633)
- Catskills, September 4, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1634)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Tour Queens and Bronx Counties, September 5, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1635)
- Republican State Convention - Rochester, New York, September 6-8, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1636)
- Health-Welfare-Mental Health - Rochester, New York, September 8, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1637)
  Cornerstone-laying for county building.
- Seneca County Republican Committee - Seneca Falls, New York, September 9, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1638)
- Women's Republican Club - Auburn, New York, September 9, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1639)
- New York Press Association - Lake George, New York, September 9, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1640)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Suffolk County, New York, September 12, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1641)
  Tour Republic Aviation, Airborne, S.M.S., Gyrodyne Corp.
- Long Island Rail Road - Lake Ronkonkoma, New York, September 12, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1642)
  Ceremonies, first run, gas turbine engine.
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Catskill, New York, September 13, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1643)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Catskill, New York, September 13, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1644)
- New York State Bridge Authority, September 13, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1645)
- New York State Association of Real Estate Boards - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 13, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1646)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 13, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1647)
- Sullivan County Reception - Cancelled, September 13, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1648)
- Remington Rand - Opening of National Training Center - Elmira, New York, September 14, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1649)
- Corning Community College - Luncheon with Educators - Corning, New York, September 14, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1650)
- New York State Council of Churches - Syracuse, New York, September 14, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1651)
  Cornerstone-laying, Council of Churches building.
- Associated Industries of New York State - Whiteface, New York, September 14, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1652)
- Steuben Parade - New York City, September 17, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1653)
  Review annual parade.
- 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - New York City, September 19, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1654)
  Breakfast with New York City Republican Committee and Republican Candidates.
- Associated Press - Albany, New York, September 19, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1655)
  New York State Association dinner.
- National Industrial Conference Board - New York City, September 19, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1656)
- Cortland Rotary - Luncheon - Cortland, New York, September 20, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1657)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Endicott, New York, September 20, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1658)
  Campaign Rally.
- Tioga County Republican Committee - Owego, New York, September 20, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1659)
  Reception and barbeque.
- New York State Mason's Dinner for Judge Louis M. Greenblott - Binghamton, New York, September 20, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1660)
- Opening of Rockefeller Headquarters - Binghamton, New York, September 20, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1661)
- Bridge, Tunnel and Turnpike Association - New York City, September 21, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1662)
  International annual meeting.
- Department of Civil Service - New York City, September 21, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1663)
  First commencement, Career Development Program.
- Willowbrook State School for Mental Defectives - Staten Island, New York, September 21, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1664)
  Practical Nursing commencement.
- State University College - Plattsburgh, New York, September 21, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1665)
  Ribbon Cutting for new dormitory.
- Airport Welcome - Massena, New York, September 22, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1666)
- Not Used (Box 45, Folder 1667)
- Massena Kiwanis - Luncheon - Massena, New York, September 22, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1668)
- Aluminum Company of America - Massena, New York, September 22, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1669)
  "Zero Defects" inaugural.
- Airport Rally - Plattsburgh, New York, September 22, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1670)
- Clinton County Republican Committee - Plattsburgh, New York, September 22, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1671)
- Touchdown Club - New York City, September 26, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1672)
- New York City - Receptions, September 26, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1673)
- New Haven Rail Road Press Conference - Greenwich, Connecticut, September 27, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1674)
- Westchester County Tour, September 27, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1675)
- State University of New York, Oneonta - Oneonta, New York, September 28, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1676)
  Dedication of Health Center.
- Otsego County Republican Committee - Oneonta, New York, September 28, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1677)
- State University Agricultural and Technical College - Delhi, New York, September 28, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1678)
  Clarke A. Sanford lecture.
- Albany, New York, September 28, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1679)
  Boys' Club - 75th Anniversary Dinner. Albany County Republican Committee - Fund raising and Testimonial Dinner for Daniel E. Button and NAR.
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Wellsville, New York, September 29, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1680)
  Worthington Pump & Machinery Co. - Tour of turbine plant. Allegany County Republican Committee - Luncheon.
- Opening of City GOP Headquarters - Olean, New York, September 29, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1681)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Dunkirk, New York, September 29, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1682)
  Tour of shopping center.
- New York State Conservation Council - Jamestown, New York, September 29, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1683)
- Cummings Lecture at the Educational Alliance - New York City, September 30, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1684)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - New York City, September 30, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1685)
  "Show of Shows."
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - West Babylon, New York, October 1, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1686)
  Headquarters opening.
- "Aviation Day" - MacArthur Airport, Islip, New York, October 1, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1687)
  Dedication of airport building terminal.
- Republican Women in Industry and the Profession - New York City, October 1, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1688)
  "Salute to Women" luncheon.
- Westchester Outdoor Exhibit - New Rochelle, New York, October 1, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1689)
- Long Island Committee for Soviet Jewry - East Meadow, New York - Cancelled, October 2, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1690)
- Pulaski Memorial Committee - Pulaski Day Parade - New York City, October 2, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1691)
- Putnam County Republican Committee - Mahopac, New York, October 2, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1692)
  Republican Women buffet.
- St. Joseph's College for Women - Golden Jubilee Dinner - Brooklyn, New York, October 3, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1693)
- Drug and Hospital Employees - New York City, October 4, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1694)
  NAR attends Local 1199 joint meeting.
- Amun-Israeli - New York City, October 4, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1695)
  Corporation luncheon.
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - New York City, October 4, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1696)
  Negro Labor Committee.
- Montgomery County, New York, October 5, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1697)
- Bishop Scully High School - Amsterdam, New York, October 5, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1698)
- Schenectady County Republican Committee - Schenectady, New York, October 5, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1699)
- Women's Republican Club - Gloversville, Fulton County, New York, October 5, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1700)
- State University Agricultural and Technical College - Cobleskill, New York, October 5, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1701)
- State of New York Library Trustees Foundation - Syracuse, New York, October 6, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1702)
- State University Agricultural and Technical College - Morrisville, New York, October 6, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1703)
  Groundbreaking.
- Colgate University - Hamilton, New York, October 6, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1704)
  Charles Dana Arts Center.
- Onondaga Republican Committee - Buffet - Onondaga, New York Camillus Republican Committee - Dinner - Camillus, New York, October 6, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1705)
- Polish Union of America - New York City, October 9, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1706)
  Annual Polish Millennium dinner.
- St. Francis College - Brooklyn, New York, October 10, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1707)
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Brooklyn, New York, October 10, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1708)
  Visit storefront.
- Double Ten Day Parade - Chinatown, New York City, October 10, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1709)
- State Supreme Court - Building Dedication - Mineola, New York, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1710)
- Hofstra University - Hempstead, New York, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1711)
  Inspects buildings, addresses students and faculty.
- East Meadow Chamber of Commerce - East Meadow, Long Island, New York, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1712)
- Caravan House - New York City, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1713)
  Dedication of Puerto Rican Library.
- Gubernatorial Campaign 1966 - Garden City, New York, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1714)
  Republican Headquarters opening; Lillian Heidleberger reception.
- Columbus Citizens Committee - Columbus Day Dinner - New York City, October 11, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1715)
- New York City Tour, October 12, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1716)
- Garment Center Congregation - Dedication - New York City, October 13, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1717)
- Rotary - New York City, October 13, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1718)
- Civil Service Employees Association - Annual Convention - Buffalo, New York, October 13, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1719)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, Inc. - Annual Dinner - New York City, October 13, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1720)